

JASON MATILLANO

Software Test Engineer / Military Officer

Contact Me

+639615173387
jason.matillano@gmail.com
Lot 6, Block 18, Uranus Street,
Brgy Taculing Bacolod,
Negros Occidental ,Philippines

Birth Date

24/Apr/1994

Other Info

Skills

Windows/ MAC/ Linux/
Ubuntu, Virtual Machine /
VirtualBox/ VMware, MS
Office/ Word/ Excel/ PPT/
PowerBI, Project Management
Tools/ Trello/ git/ github/
gitlab, GoogleDocs/Sheet/
AppScript, WebDev/ HTML/
CSS/ Javascript/ VUEJs

LanguagesEnglish, Tagalog, Japanese ,

Summary

I'm a graduate of Bachelor of Science in Electronics and Communications Engineering from University of St. La Salle. Two (2) years work experience in the Software Development Industry as a Software Test Engineer and four (4) years of experience in the Military as an Officer.

Education

University of Saint La Salle Bacolod

2011 - 2016

BSECE

Studied Bachelor of Science in Electronics and Communications Engineering at University of St La Salle Bacolod (USLS-Bacolod). I took and Passed the ECE Board Exam after Graduation.

Experience

Accenture Cebu

Mar 2017 - Apr 2018

Data Analyst

Support Client's Business Operation by providing data analysis and interpretation on the team's performance and outputs.

Windsgate

May 2018 - Apr 2019

Software Test Engineer

Conduct test and evaluation on the software applications that the company develop for our clients. Provide recommendations to the team according to the client's feedback.

Philippine Navy

Bisaya

Interest

Music, Travelling, Gym, Running, Reading 2019 - 2023

Officer

Provide the Philippine Navy's requirements for operations, logistics and manpower in different

Commands/Headquarters/Bases in the Region. Ensure the accomplishment of the organization's mission of protecting the territorial integrity and preserving peace.

Naval Training Institute (Philippine Navy)

Jun 2020 - Jul 2022

Training Officer

Recommend on the Drafting/Updating of Istruction Materials and other important documents. Administering activities and conduct assessments to identify areas of improvement.

Orienting Students to their role and responsibilities within the Institute. Supervise the students for the whole duration of the course. Coordinate with Course Director and Instructors for the scheduling of classes and exams.

Naval Installation Command (Philippine Navy)

Jul 2022 - Aug 2023

Command Adjutant

Publishes the official orders of the unit. Responsible for supervising clerks and other administrative personnel, submits reports to higher headquarters, handles official correspondence, and maintains records.

Projects

Windsgate Inc.

2017 - 2018

Windsgate Website

Development, update and maintenance of Windsgate Website.

Windsgate Inc

2018 - 2019

WebDev Project Management

Manage web develop projects using Trello Management App.